{
  "id": 301,
  "themeId": 3,
  "name": "Writing and Reading Gender â€“ Quiz 1",
  "description": "Practice Gender vocabulary and grammar through writing and reading exercises.",
  "version": "2.2.3",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How do you say "She"?",
      "options": ["A. Elle", "B. Sa", "C. Lui", "D. All of the above"],
      "correctAnswer": "A. Elle"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say "He"?",
      "options": ["A. Lui", "B. Il", "C. Ils", "D. Leur"],
      "correctAnswer": "B. Il"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say "They"? (plural, feminine)",
      "options": ["A. Elle", "B. Elles", "C. Ellent", "D. Eles"],
      "correctAnswer": "B. Elles"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say "His"?",
      "options": ["A. Son", "B. Sa", "C. Le", "D. Lui"],
      "correctAnswer": "A. Son"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"The\"? (singular, feminine)",
      "options": ["A. Sa", "B. Leur", "C. La", "D. Les"],
      "correctAnswer": "C. La"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"The\"? (singular, masculine)",
      "options": ["A. Lui", "B. Les", "C. Son", "D. Le"],
      "correctAnswer": "D. Le"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"Her motorcycle\"?",
      "options": ["A. Sa moto", "B. La moto", "C. Son moto", "D. Elle moto"],
      "correctAnswer": "A. Sa moto"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"His death\"?",
      "options": ["A. Son mort", "B. Sa mort", "C. Leur mort", "D. Il est mort"],
      "correctAnswer": "B. Sa mort"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"her hair\" ?",
      "options": ["A. Son cheveux", "B. Sa cheveu", "C. Ses cheveux", "D. Leur cheveu"],
      "correctAnswer": "C. Ses cheveux",
      "explanation": "French uses the singular form (cheveu) to refer to a single strand of hair, while the plural form (cheveux) refers to all the hair on one's head."
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say "They"? (plural, non binary)",
      "options": ["A. Iels", "B. Yels", "C. Elils", "D. All of the above"],
      "correctAnswer": "D. All of the above",
      "explanation": "This spelling is not mainstream but one might encounter it in France."
    }
  ]
}